'use strict';
const STORE = [
  {question: 'Which Pennsylvania town is the Office set?',
    answers: [
    'Pittsburgh',
    'Philadelphia',
    'Scranton',
    'Harrisburg'
  ],
  correctAnswer: 'Scranton'
  },
  {question: 'Who is Pam first engaged to?',
    answers: [
      'Roy',
      'Michael',
      'Jim',
      'Toby'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'Roy'
  },
  {
  question: 'How long did Jim wait to buy an engagement ring when he and Pam started dating?',
    answers: [
      'A month',
      'A year',
      '6 months',
      'A week'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'A week'
  },
  {question: 'Which country does Toby go to when he quits?',
    answers: [
      'Mexico',
      'Costa Rica',
      'Cuba',
      'Jamaica'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'Costa Rica'
  },
  {question: 'What does Pam go back to school for?',
    answers: [
      'Business',
      'Graphic Design',
      'Teaching',
      'Computer Science'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'Graphic Design'
  },
  {question: 'What is grown at Schrute Farms?',
    answers: [
      'Beets',
      'Corn',
      'Potatoes',
      'Tomatoes'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'Beets'
  },
  {question: 'What official title does Dwight hold?',
    answers: [
      'Assistant Regional Manager',
      'Regional Manager',
      'Accountant',
      'Assistant to the Regional Manager'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'Assistant to the Regional Manager'
  },
  {question: 'What nickname does Andy give Jim?',
    answers: [
      'Sport',
      'Squirt',
      'Plop',
      'Tuna'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'Tuna'
    },
    {question: 'From which college did Andy graduate?',
      answers: [
        'Princeton',
        'Harvard',
        'Cornell',
        'Yale'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'Cornell'
    },
    {question: 'Which restaurant is Pam banned from?',
      answers: [
        'Applebee\'s',
        'Chilli\'s',
        'Red Lobster',
        'Olive Garden'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'Chilli\'s'
    }
]
